Anup Timsina

AI/ML Enthuisast

• +977 9825988006 • timsinaanup23@gmail.com

Dedicated Data Analyst with a passion for Artificial Intelligence and Machine Learning, skilled in developing data analysis pipelines and collaborating on AI mobile development projects. Experienced in delivering coding training sessions to enhance programming skills in students.

EXPERIENCE

Data Analyst Jhapa

TechDebugger Pvt. Ltd Sep, 2023 - Present

- Collaborated with teams in AI mobile development.
- Developed data analysis pipelines.
- Collaborated on data-driven solutions.

Coding Trainer Kathmandu

Skilltootr Jun, 2023 - Present

- Conduct virtual training sessions on programming concepts.
- Focus on both theory and practical applications.
- Upskill students to enhance their programming skills.

EDUCATION

Bachelors in Information Technology

Nov, 2019 - Sep, 2023 Texas College of Management and IT

Intermediate (Specialization: Computer Engineering)

Damak

Kathmandu

Himalaya Secondary School Jun, 2017 - Jun, 2019

TRAINING/CERTIFICATIONS

Al For Everyone 2020

Coursera

https://coursera.org/verify/MDBSGTQZPWPS

Google IT Automation with Python

2020

Coursera

https://www.coursera.org/account/accomplishments/specialization/certificate/SLEZZYDDYLX8

Data Analysis with Python

2023

Free Code Camp

freecodecamp.org/certification/timsinaanup/data-analysis-with-python-v7

SKILLS

Artificial intelligence and Machine learning, Programming Language (Python, HTML, CSS, JavaScript, SQL), Data Structures and Algorithm, Decision making skill, Time Management skill, Problem Solving, Flexibility,, Good interpersonal and communication skills with leadership quality, Project and team management

LANGUAGE

Nepali, English, Hindi